tuneup360.com 2014-12-16

# TuneUp360.com-PC Tuneup and Repair Online

Our approach to privacy

The following privacy policy describes the information and privacy practices for TuneUp360, services provided at your home or office, 

TuneUp360.com

and other retail locations. This privacy policy describes how TuneUp360 will collect and use your information. 

We recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner. TuneUp360 has created this policy to inform you how your Personal Information will be treated if you use the Site or order our Services. In general, you can visit the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personally identifiable information from you.

This privacy policy may not apply to Web sites that are accessible through the 

TuneUp360.com

may contain links to other sites operated by third parties including. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of those our sites to learn how we collect, use, share and secure your information.

When you provide a TuneUp360 with your personal information, you consent to the information practices described in this policy.

**What information does TuneUp360 collect?**

"Personal Information" is information that   
( **i** ) is recorded in any form;   
( **ii** ) is about you, or pertains to you; and   
( **iii** ) can be linked to you. Personal Information includes information like your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing.

**When does TuneUp360 store information?**

We may store any information entered into the website by users of the website, or supplied to us by those with whom we do business. For example, you may be asked to provide personal information when you schedule an appointment for services; purchase products; contact TuneUp360 call centers; initiate a chat session; participate in a sweepstakes, promotion, or survey; and/or participate in other activities with TuneUp360 entities. Of course, if you are a service provider, you want to join us, you should supply your service information to us.

Use of Personal Information

In general, Personal Information is used by us   
( **i** ) to register you for our Services,   
( **ii** ) to respond to your requests and provide the Services to you,  
( **iii** ) to improve the features, performance and support of the Services, and   
( **iv** ) to offer you additional information, opportunities, and functionality. We may also use your Personal Information to provide you with promotional e-mails, should you request to receive such communications from us.

TuneUp360 personnel and any third party contractors working for or with TuneUp360 in providing the Service only get access to any of the customer information (including any Personal Information therein) on a need-to-know basis and are under contractual obligations to keep the confidentiality of such information.

TuneUp360 may also collect and create aggregate information about customers, sales, traffic patterns, and data about our services and systems, and use such information internally and provide it to third parties at our discretion, but this aggregate information will not include any Personal Information.

TuneUp360 will share your service information with customers online, in order to users find your information.

Information disclosed

We may supply information to those with whom we do business, but only for purposes in connection with the operation of the TuneUp360 service.

We may supply information in response to a court order, subpoena, or upon demand of the government when we believe that the government is legitimately entitled to make such a demand. For example, the taxation authorities are entitled to see certain information.

We may supply information at our discretion when we sincerely believe it is in the best interests of the data subject, or in the best interests of society as a whole, for us to do so. For example, we may supply information if we believe it might help avert a crime or prevent a suicide.

We may share aggregated non-personal information (such as service statistics) with anyone. If you are a service provider, in order to users finding your information, all your service information provided to TuneUp360 may be shared with customers online. 

**How does TuneUp360 secure the personal information?**

Security

Our Services help diagnose and resolve technology problems that you may have. TuneUp360 uses several types of software: the first type provides computer system information to TuneUp360 which helps us to identify, diagnose and resolve the technology problem that you have encountered and/or problems that may arise in the future, the second type generally consists of utilities and other tools to improve computer performance and help solve your personal technology problem, and the third type allows TuneUp360 Agents to remotely control your computer and modify its settings or software in our attempt to solve your technology problem. By ordering our Services, you are giving express permission to TuneUp360 to download and use the software described above (the "TuneUp360 Software"). Depending on the Services that you order, the TuneUp360 Software may allow us to temporarily take control of your computer and modify your computer settings to resolve your personal technology problem . For other Services, the TuneUp360 Software will report non-personal information about your PC's performance and configuration to you and to TuneUp360. For such Services, the TuneUp360 Software will run on a regular basis, but only after you elect to run the TuneUp360 Software and report your PC information to yourself and to TuneUp360. In every instance, TuneUp360 will solely use the TuneUp360 Software and the information that it provides to attempt to identify and resolve your existing and potential personal technology problem(s) and use reasonable efforts to limit its access of your Personal Information while performing the Services and only after you have given us permission to do so. However, in the course of providing the Services to you, TuneUp360 may inadvertently see, access, or being exposed to Personal Information on your computer. You are responsible for and TuneUp360 has no liability for securing and backing up your computer network, all information stored on your computer and all software on your computer.

Monitoring of the Services

TuneUp360 has the right, but no obligation, to monitor and record the performance of the Services, including telephone calls and online sessions with the TuneUp360 Software and you hereby acknowledge and agree to such activities. TuneUp360 may use the data collected during such recordings for purposes of improving customer service, internal training, and internal market research and will handle such data as described in the previous paragraph with respect to Personal Information that may be contained in such data. TuneUp360 will delete such data after a reasonable amount of time. 

Cookies

Our website sends cookies to your browser, for example to help the login/logout process work smoothly. You are free to set your web browser to accept or reject these cookies.

Our website may include links to advertisements, scripts or content from other sites. Those other sites may send cookies to your browser. You are free to set your web browser to accept or reject these third-party cookies.

We currently use Google for our advertising. You can opt out of Google's advertising cookies if you wish.

Webserver logs

We use the webserver logs for business purposes including combating spam and producing business statistics.

Countriess

Our webserver and database are currently in the United States, but this may change. We may send information to, or process it in, other countries.

Updates

This Privacy Policy may be revised by us from time to time. If we decide to change our privacy practices, we will post those changes on this page and post a notice on the home page of the Site so that you are always kept informed of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. If at any point we make a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will notify registered users by way of an e-mail. You will have a choice to opt out of any new or different uses of your Personal Information. We will use your information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. Changes will normally be notified here 30 days before they take effect.

**Contact TuneUp360**

We are committed to protecting the privacy of the information you provide to us. If you have any comments, questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or your information, [Please Contact Our Support Team](http://support.tuneup360.com/index.php?submod=ticket&method=onlineform). Most enquiries are dealt with in a day or two, but please allow a few weeks in exceptional circumstances.

Choice and Opt-Out

If you no longer wish to receive the Company's promotional communications, you may "opt-out" of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or by e-mailing the Company at [webmaster@TuneUp360.com ](mailto:webmaster@TuneUp360.com).
